ZEESHAN NAWAZ

Android Developer

UI Designer

PROFILE

I'm primarily a Mobile Applications Developer, passionate about building beautiful & functional mobile apps, with over 3 years of own experience and 1 year of work experience So far in my career, I have worked on about 5+ mobile apps. I started out as an Android Developer, working on Java/Kotlin. Also, I have also work on C Sharp Development. Currently I'm seller at Fiverr.

CONTACT

- **3** 03205582355
- fb.com/zeeshu10
- ≥ zeeshann0022@gmail.com
- zeeshan0022.github.io/ZPortfolio

EXPERIENCE

Android Internships

OCT 2020 - JAN 2021

I have done Internship at Cottage app studio in Android Studio. In 3 months of Internships, I highly learned about android development their API's etc.

Mobile Shop

2017-2018

In the field of Mobile I worked in Mobile Shop of sell and purchase. Meanwhile, I learned little bit about of Mobile Software Flashing.

SKILLS

- Android Development (Kotlin)
- Web Development (Asp.net)
- C#/ C++
- UI Designer (Adobe XD)
- Desktop Application (C#, Java)

Android Own Experience

2018-2022

Basically, I have much own experience about Android Development, their API's, SDK, Architecture MVP.

Certification

- Huawei Seed for the Future Program 2020
- Huawei Seed for the Future Program 2021 (5th Position)
- Digi skills certificate of SEO, Graphic Designer, WordPress

EDUCATION

Intermediate

2015-2016

Punjab Group of College of Commerce RWP 811/1100

Graduation

2018-2022

PMAS Arid Agriculture University RWP CGPA: 3.88